A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
- Artists' Files, bulk 1955-1999; circa 1907-2006; Series 3; 39.1 Linear feet Boxes 24-62, 95-96
  - Swindell, Geoffrey, Correspondence and Sales, 1982-1998 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Swindell, Geoffrey, Reproductions, 1978-1986 (Box 57, Folder 10-11)
  - Swinden, Albert, undated; 1967-1988 (Box 57, Folder 12-15)
  - Swinden, Albert, Original Photos and Negatives, circa 1986 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Swinden, Albert, Originals, 1962-1986 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Tack, Augustus Vincent, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Takal, Peter, 1955-1959 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Talasnik, Stephen, circa 1999 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Tannenbaum, Samuel, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Terris, Albert, 1957-1962 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Thomas, Howard, 1955-1958 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Thorne, Joan (Box 57)
    - Accounting - Sold Invoices, 1985-1992 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Appraisals/Resales, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - [Artist Binder], 1980s-1991 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Biography, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - [Catalogs and Press], 1979-1990 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Thorne, Joan (Box 58)
    - Catalogs and Press, 1979-1991 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
    - Clients, 1985-1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Consignments Out, 1980s-1992 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Expenses, circa 1986 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - General, 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Installation Photographs, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1991 (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
    - [Photographic Materials], circa 1977-1990s (Box 58, Folder 11-16)
    - Press, 1980s-1991 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Prints, 1990; 1985 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Returned to Artist, 1994; 1992 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Traveling, circa 1985-1989 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Tobias, Alan, 1964-1970 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
  - Torr, Helen, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Touster, Irwin, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Townley, Hugh, 1956-1957 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Trieff, Selina (Box 59)
    - Accounting - Sold Invoices, 1985-1990 (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
    - Advertising Account, circa 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - [Biographical Information], 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Catalog, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - [Consignments, Loans, In/Out, and Returned to Artist], 1987-1992 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Listings, 1988-1990 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1984-1993 (Box 59, Folder 14-16)
    - [Photographic Materials], 1980s (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Press [Binder], 1970s-1980s (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Traveling, circa 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Truex, Van Day, 1968-1975 (Box 59, Folder 20-21)
  - Truex, Van Day (Chauvet), 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Utley, Windsor, 1955-1960 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Valkus, James, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 59, Folder 24-25)
  - Valledor, Leo, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Van Leyden, Ernest and Karen, 1955-1957 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Vander Sluis, George, 1956-1958 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Vedder, Elihu, 1966-1978 (Box 59, Folder 29-31)
  - Vedder, Elihu, 1974-1982 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Velde, Geer van, 1955-1956 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Verdon, Angela, 1997-2002 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Verdon, Angela, Prices, Inventory and Consignments from A.V., 1982-1993 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Verdon, Angela, Reproductions, circa 1980s-1993 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
  - Vivone, Linda, 1969-1973 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - von Morisse, Andre, 1996-1999 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Walker, Stuart, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Walton, William, 1964-1971 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Walton, William, Publicity, 1961-1967 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Ward, John, 1982-2001 (Box 60, Folder 12-13)
  - Watkins, Carlton, circa 1978 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Weber, Max, 1962; 1968-1976 (Box 60, Folder 15-16)
  - Weinreg, Agnes, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Weinrich, Agnes, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - West, Benjamin, 1921; 1951-1963 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Whalen, Richard, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - White, John Alexander, undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - White, Minor, 1973-1976 (Box 60, Folder 22-24)
  - White, Robert, 1956-1978 (Box 60, Folder 25-28)
  - White, Robert (1978), 1975-1983 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - White, Robert, Photographs, undated (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - White, Robert, Scrapbook, 1957-1967 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - White, Robert, Scrapbook, 1960s-1992 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
  - Wicht, John von, 1986-1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Willard, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Wilmarth, Christopher, 1968-1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, Jane, 1965-1977 (Box 61, Folder 7-11)
  - Wilson, Jane, Artist Binder, 1968-1971 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Winer, Margery, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Wo Yue-Kee, Henry, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Wright, Joseph, undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Wyeth, N.C., 1961-1964 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Yampolsky, Phyllis, 1976-1980 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Young, Becky, 1971-1984 (Box 61, Folder 18-22)
  - Young, Becky (1978-1979), 1973-1980 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Young, Becky, Press Material, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Yrisarry, Mario, 1960s (Box 62, Folder 2-5)
  - Yrisarry, Mario, Clippings and Biographies, circa 1965-1967 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Ziegler, Laura, 1956-1959 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Zlamany, Brenda, circa 1995-1997 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Zolotow, Harry, 1957-1958 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Various Artists, 1955-1990s (Box 62, Folder 10-13)
  - Restricted Folder (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Berke, Ernest, Oversized Color Photographs, circa 1981 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    Oversized material from Box 26, Folder 23
  - Reinhardt, Ad, Oversized Printed Materials, 1966-1967 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Oversized material from Box 52, Folder 13
  - Steir, Pat, Oversized Printed Material [David Slivka], 1963 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Oversized material from Box 56, Folder 20
- Artwork Files, bulk 1983-2009; circa early 1900s-2011; Series 4; 9.3 Linear feet Boxes 63-71, 94, 101
  Artwork Files documents sales, consignments, and loans of artwork through agreements and contracts; condition reports; correspondence; invoices and receipts; photographs of artwork; shipping records; and photocopied printed material and other documentation. Most photographs are described on the back with the following: artist name, title of artwork, artwork date, size, and medium. This series requires written permission from the donor in order to access.
  Folders are arranged according to the original order, loosely in alphabetical order by artist's last name and by title of the artwork. A handful of folders of miscellaneous materials related to artwork are filed at the end of the series.
  - Albert, Ernest - Alexander, John White, 1980s-2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, John White, 1980s-2009 (Box 63, Folder 2-3)
  - Alma-Tadema, Sir Lawrence - Ames, Ezna, 1957-2001 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Ames, Ezna - Anshutz, Thomas, 1987-2001 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Anshutz, Thomas, 1979-2000s (Box 63, Folder 6-7)
  - Anshutz, Thomas - Avery, Milton, 1960s-2007 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Beard, William - Benjamin, Gershon, 1990-2003 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Bellows, George - Thomas Hart Benton Estate, 1975-2002 (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1979-2008; 1969 (Box 63, Folder 12-14)
  - Bensell, Frederick - Berninghaus, Oscar, 1979-2002; 1960s (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Bernstein, Theresa - Blakelock, Ralph, 1979-2005; 1929 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Blakelock, Ralph - Bluemner, Oscar, 1985-2007 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Bluemner, Oscar, 1987-2008 (Box 64, Folder 2-4)
  - Bluhm, Norman, 2004-2008 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Blume, Peter - Bonheur, Rosa, 1981-2004 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Briscoe, Franklin D. - Burns, J., 1980s-2009 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Butler, Theodore E. - Bridgman, Frederick A., 1977-2005 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Buttersworth, James E. - Carles, Arthur Beecher, 1959; 1983-2006 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Carles, Arthur Beecher - Carlsen, Emil, 1959; 1981-2000 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Carlsen, Emil - Chase, William Merritt, 1963; 1985-2006 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Chase, William Merritt - Cooper, Colin Campbell, 1979-2006 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Cope, George - Crane, Bruce, 1980-2000 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Crawford, Ralston - Davies, Arthur, 1969-2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Davies, Arthur B. - Davis, Stuart, 1986-1997 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Stuart - De Haas, Mauritz Frederik Hendrik, 1993-2006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Delacroix, Eugene - Dickinson, Edwin, 1978-2008 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Dickinson, Edwin, 1985-2005; circa 1968 (Box 65, Folder 5-6)
  - Dickinson, Preston - Dove, Arthur, 1988-2002 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Drewes, Werner - Du Bois, Guy Pène, 1960s; 1979-2006 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Du Bois, Guy Pène, circa 1945; 1983-2008; 1963-1967 (Box 65, Folder 9-14)
  - Du Bois, William Pène - Eakins, Thomas, 1992-2004 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Earl, Ralph - Farny, Henry, 1992-2007 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Ferguson, Nancy M. - Fisher, Alvan, 1988-1996 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Flag, James M. - Fuller, George, 1977; 1992-2006 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Fuller, Henry B. - Gay, Walter, 1973-2007 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Gay, Walter, 1980-2009 (Box 66, Folder 5-10)
  - Gay, Walter - Glackens, William, 1981-2007; 1968 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Gifford, Sanford Robinson - Glintenkamp, Henry J., 1987-2002 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Glintenkamp, Henry J. - Grabach, John, 1986-2006 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Grabach, John - Garner, Luis, 1981-2000 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Graves, Abbott Fuller - Guy, James, 1986-2000 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Guy, Seymour Joseph - Hartley, Marsden, 1922; 1992-2008; 1974-1978 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Hartley, Marsden - Hassam, Childe, 1986-2005; 1962 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Hassam, Childe - Hawthorne, Charles, 1986-2002; 1958 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Hays, William Jacob - Hennings, Ernest Martin, 1980-2000; 1972 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Henri, Robert - Henry, E.L., 1977-2004 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Herzog, Herman - Hirsch, Joseph, 1969-1973; 1992-2003 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Hirsch, Stephan - Hoffman, Charles, 1993-2000 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Holty, Carl - Horton, William S., 1983-2007 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Hubard, William J. - Hunt, William Morris, 1949; circa 1970s-1990s (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Huntington, Daniel - Jenkins, George W., 1908; 1950s; 1976-2005 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Johannes, Georgius J. - Johnson, David, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, David - Johnson, Joshua, 1971; 1984-2001 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Frank Tenny - Keith, William, 1970; 1993; 2000-2008 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Keith, William - King, Paul, 1987-2002 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - King, Jessie Marion - Kuhn, Walt, 1986-2002 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo - La Barre Goodwin, Richard, circa 1970s-2006 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Lachaise, Gaston - La Farge, John, circa 1970s-2003 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - La Farge, John, 1982-2003 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - La Farge, John - Latour, Fantin, 1978-1996 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Lawman, Jasper Holman - Leigh, W.R., 1987-2005 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Leigh, William Robinson - Lorenz, Richard, 1984-2007 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Lorenz, Richard - Lucioni, Luigi, 1987-2003 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Lucioni, Luigi, 1990-2004 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Lucioni, Luigi - MacCoy, Guy, 1980s-2004 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - MacRae, Elmer - MacRae, Emma Fordyce, 1991-2004 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - MacRae, Emma Fordyce - Maril, Herman, 1982-2007; 1936-1954 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Maril, Herman, 1999-2003 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Maril, Herman - Marin, John, 1988-2005; 1979 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Marsh, Reginald - Maurer, Alfred, 1988-2000 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Mayer, Bena Frank - Mead, Larkin, 1984-2002 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Meiere, Hildreth - Melchers, Gari, 1980s-2006 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Melchers, Gari - Millar, A.T., 1983-2006 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Alfred Jacob - Moran, Peter, 1970s; 1989-2002 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Moran, Thomas - Murphy, Hermann Dudley, 1977-2005 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Murphy, Hermann Dudley, 1985-1999 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Murphy, John F. - Noheimer, Mathias, circa 1974-2009 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia - Parsons, Orrin Sheldon, 1974-2007 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Pattison, James W. - Peale, Charles Willson, 1992-2004; 1970s (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Peale, James - Peale, Rembrandt, 1967-1998 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Peale, Sarah - Perry, Lilla C., 1987-1997 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Perrine, Van Dearing - Philipp, Robert, 1982-2002; 1972 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Picknell, George - Poor, Henry Varnum, 1990-2005 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Pope, Alexander - Potthast, Edward, 1987-2001 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Prendergast, Maurice - Redfield, Edward, 1986-2003 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Rehn, Frank Knox Morton - Remington, Frederick, 1992-2002 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Remington, Frederick, 1967-1999 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Remington, Frederick - Resika, Paul, 1950s-2007 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Ribcowsky, Dey de - Rico y Ortega, Martin, 1979-2005 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Rindisbacher - Robertson, Archibald, circa 1980s-2003 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Roesen, Severin - Russell, Charles Marion, 1979-1999 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Russell, Morgan - Schille, Alice, circa 1980s-2002 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Schille, Alice - Sharples, James, 1980s-2005 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Shayer, William - Sheeler, Charles, 1988-2002 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Sheeler, Charles, 1984-1993; circa 1949 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Shinn, Everett, 1958-1959; 1975-2010 (Box 70, Folder 2-4)
  - Shinn, Everett - Smith, Henry P., 1985-2006 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Walter Granville - Spencer, Robert, 1974; 1983-2006 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Spencer, Robert - Stella, Joseph, 1994-2003 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Stella, Joseph - Stuart, Gilbert, 1960s; 1983-1995; circa early 1900s (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Suba, Miklos, 1944; 1992-2007 (Box 70, Folder 9-10)
  - Suba, Miklos - Symons, George Gardner, 1977-1981; 1990-2008 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Tarbell, Edmund Charles - Torr, Helen, 1990-2010 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Torr, Helen, circa 1980s-2008 (Box 70, Folder 13-15)
  - Troye, Edward - Voorhees, Clark G., circa 1960s-2002 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Vytlacil, Vaclav, 1987-2007 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Vytlacil, Vaclav - Wall, William A., 1972; 1989-2006 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Walter, Martha - Weeks, Edwin Lord, 1986-2004 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Weinrich, Agnes - Weber, Max, 1987-2000 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Weber, Max - Weston, Harold, 1994-2007; 1960s (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Weston, Harold - Whittredge, Worthington, 1977-2007 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - White, Robert - Wiggins, Guy, 1990-2007 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Wiggins, Guy - Williams, J.L., 1986-2005 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, John - Wuermer, Carl, 1997-2004; 1960-1970 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Wood, Grant - Wyeth, Andrew, 1992-2005; circa 1928 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, 1993-2008 (Box 71, Folder 12-15)
  - Wyeth, Andrew - Wyeth, Jamie, 1995-2009 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Wyeth, Jamie, 2003-2007 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Wyeth, Jamie - Wyeth, N.C., 1992-2009 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Wyeth, N.C. - Zorach, William, 1994-2005 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Art Fairs, 2001-2007 (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 100, Folder 1
  - [Bronzes], 1981-1984 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - [Storage Maintenance], 2011 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Clippings, Art Fairs, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials from Box 94, Folder 2
- Financial Records, circa 1937-1993; Series 5; 4.5 Linear feet Boxes 72-76, 96
  This series contains check stub books from the mid-late 1950s; a consignments ledger; price lists; sales receipts from 1959-1964 and 1969-1984 (missing 1974); sales ledgers from 1962-1969; scattered banking, financial, and tax records; and, banking and expense records for the Four Seasons Charter Corp. Additional sales records are found in Artwork Files and additional bills from 1950s-mid-1960s are found in Alphabetical Files.
  - Bank Statements, The Bank of New York, 1980s-1992 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - Bills, A-Z, Miscellaneous, 1955-1968 (Box 72, Folder 3-21)
  - Check Stub Books (Dec. 1954 - Jan. 1956; Jan. - Dec. 1956), 1954-1956; (2 books) (Box 72, Folder 22-23)
  - Check Stub Books (Apr. - July 1958) (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Check Stub Books, Duveen-Graham, 1956-1958; (2 books) (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Consignments Ledger, circa 1937-1965 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Consignments Lists, 1956-1961 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Credits, 1954-1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Deposit Slips, Bankers Trust, 1963-1965 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Four Seasons Charter Corp. (Box 73)
    - Accounting, 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 7-8)
    - Banking Statements, circa 1964-1967 (Box 73, Folder 9-10)
    - Banking Statements and Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 11-14)
  - Four Seasons Charter Corp. (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Peter Vandersloot Expense Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
    - Yacht - "Stranger" (1965), 1964-1965 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Yacht - "Stranger" (1966) (Box 74, Folder 5-6)
    - Yacht - "Stranger" (1971), 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 7-13)
  - General Ledger, Duveen-Graham, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Invoices, Miscellaneous [Graham Modern], 1986-1992 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Invoices, Recent [Graham Modern], 1993 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Photo Charges, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - [Price Lists], 1967-1973 (Box 74, Folder 18-19)
  - Price Lists, 1971-1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Price Lists (Box 75)
    - [Back Room], circa 1973-1984 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - First Floor, 1979-1983 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Second Floor, 1987; 1973-1983 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Ceramics Exhibitions, circa 1985-1993 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Paintings (1990), 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Paintings (1991), 1990-1993 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Prices, 1969-1971 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Prices Quoted, 1986-1991 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Receipts, 1979-1982 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Resale Certificates, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Sales (1969-1984), 1968-1984 (Box 75, Folder 12-25)
  - Sales, G.R. [Georgia Riley?], 1979 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Sales and Purchases Ledgers (Jan. 1962 - Dec. 1966; Jan. 1967 - Jan. 1969), 1962-1969; (2 ledgers) (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
  - Sales Receipts, 1959-1965 (Box 76, Folder 3-5)
  - Sales Tax (1962) [and Sales Receipts], 1961-1964 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Stock Shares, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Tax Items, 1984-1985 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Taxes (Federal), 1955-1963 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Year End Sales (1991-1992), 1993 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    Oversized material housed in Box 96, Folder 4
  - Oversized, Year End Sales (1991-1992), 1993 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Oversized material from Box 76, Folder 10
- Inventory Records, circa 1954-1993; Series 6; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 76-78, 96
  The bulk of this series are inventory cards from mid-1950s-1970s arranged very loosely in alphabetical order by artist's last name. Researchers are encouraged to consult the entire span of the inventory cards, rather than relying on alphabetical order. Also found are lists of inventory, often with notations and prices.
  - Inventory Cards, circa 1955-1971 (Box 76, Folder 11-16)
  - Inventory Cards, circa 1955-1971 (Box 77, Folder 1-11)
  - Inventory Cards, circa 1955-1971 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Inventory Cards, A-Z, circa 1954-1957 (Box 78, Folder 2-4)
  - Inventory Lists, 1958-1967 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Oversized material housed in Box 96, Folder 5
  - Inventory, By Subject, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Stock Lists, 1950s (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Oversized, Inventory Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    Oversized material from Box 78, Folder 6
- Coe Kerr Gallery Records Regarding Wyeths, 1964-1988; Series 7; 2.7 Linear feet Boxes 78-80, 97
  Found is material created and gathered by Coe Kerr Gallery regarding exhibitions of Jamie Wyeth's work at the gallery and of his traveling exhibitions. Also found is limited material regarding exhibitions of Andrew Wyeth and N.C. Wyeth. Materials include correspondence, photographs, exhibition printed materials, and extensive newspaper clippings regarding exhibitions, primarily from clippings services.
  - Clippings (Box 78)
    - Coe Kerr Gallery, 1976-1978 (Box 78, Folder 9-11)
    - Wyeth, Andrew, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 12-18)
    - Wyeth, Andrew, Show in Japan, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Wyeth, Jamie, 1974-1975; 1967 (Box 78, Folder 20-22)
  - Clippings (Box 79)
    - Wyeth, Jamie, 1974-1977; 1967 (Box 79, Folder 1-7)
    - Wyeth, Jamie, [Exhibition] (May 2, 1975) (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Wyeth, Jamie, Exhibition at Coe Kerr Gallery, 1976-1977 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Wyeth, Jamie, Opening at Coe Kerr Gallery, 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Wyeth, N.C., 1975-1981 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Jamie Wyeth at Coe Kerr Gallery, 1976-1988 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions (Box 79)
    - "Jamie Wyeth Recent Paintings" (Nov. 7-25, 1974), 1966 (Box 79, Folder 13-14)
    - "Andy Warhol and Jamie Wyeth: Portraits of Each Other", 1974-1980 (Box 79, Folder 15-30)
  - Exhibitions (Box 80)
    - Jamie Wyeth, "Portraits", 1976 (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
    - Jamie Wyeth, "Portraits" (July 17-27, 1980; Monte Carlo) (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Jamie Wyeth, Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Sept. 19 - Dec. 14, 1980) (Box 80, Folder 5)
      Oversized material housed in Box 97, Folder 1
    - N.C. Wyeth (Oct. 14 - Nov. 28, 1980) (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Jamie Wyeth, Pennsylvania Academy Show (Sept. 18, 1980 - Jan. 1981), circa 1980 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, London and Japan, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, Paris, 1974-1977 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Wyeth, Jamie, 1964-1981 (Box 80, Folder 10-12)
  - Wyeth, Jamie (Box 80)
    - Account, 1975-1978 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Adelson Graphics, 1980s (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Catalog Prints, circa 1980 (Box 80, Folder 15-16)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Exhibition, 1978-1980 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs and Biographies, circa 1970s-1982 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Notes, circa 1976-1979 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Rudolph Nureyev Portrait, circa 1977 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Omaha, 1975; 1980 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Omaha Clippings, 1980; 1974-1975 (Box 80, Folder 24-25)
    - Photo Captions and Credit Lines, circa 1974 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 80, Folder 27-31)
    - President Kennedy Portrait, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Publicity Correspondence, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Arnold Schwarzenneger Portrait, circa 1977 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Studies of President Carter, circa 1977 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Transparencies, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Oversized Scrapbook, Jamie Wyeth Exhibition at Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Sept. 19 - Dec. 14, 1980) (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Oversized material from Box 80, Folder 5
- Printed Materials, 1949-2006; 1821; 1815; Series 8; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 81-82, 97
  Exhibition catalogs, books, announcements, magazines, clippings, postcards, posters and other printed materials related to artists, John Graham & Sons exhibitions, and exhibitions by Graham artists held at other galleries and museums are housed in this series. Also found is an 1815 fifty cent note which was redeemed in 1821. Additional printed materials are found in Artists' Files.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of materials.
  - [Advertisements], APF, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Auction Catalogs, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Books, "Jacobsen's Sixth Painting and Bronze Price Guide", 1983 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Books, "Seven Decades: Crosscurrents in Modern Art, 1895-1965" (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Brochures, 1998-1999 (Box 81, Folder 5)